careerjet.co.in 2009-12-06

# Careerjet Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to Careerjet Ltd ("Careerjet"). This Privacy Policy explains how Careerjet collects, uses, and discloses the personal information you may provide while using its website - http://www.careerjet.co.uk - (the "Website").

#### Browsing Information

When you use the Careerjet site, our servers may collect information indirectly and automatically about your activities while visiting the site, including the web pages you view and the times you view them and information about the browser you are using. We use this browsing information to personalize aspects of your job search experience, for system administration purposes and to improve the Website.

#### Personal Information You Specifically Provide

You can generally visit our Website without revealing any personally identifiable information about yourself. However, in certain sections of this Website, we may ask you to submit personally identifiable information such as your name, email address, and your CV. Your personally identifiable information will only be used to deliver certain information or services that you have requested such as job alerts, for system administration purposes and also to improve the Website. In each job alert email we send you, we provide a method to unsubscribe from future emails.

#### Disclosure of Personal Information

We do not disclose personal information to third parties in the normal course of operations, unless you specifically ask the Website to do so, for example when submitting your application to a recruiter through Careerjet or when making your CV searchable to be viewed by recruiters.   
Under certain circumstances, however, we could be legally obliged to disclose information to the government or other third parties and if Careerjet becomes part of another organisation, that organisation will possess the personal information collected by Careerjet and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Security

To help protect the confidentiality of your personal information, Careerjet employs security measures appropriate to the sensitivity of the information. Nevertheless, security and privacy risks cannot be entirely eliminated and Careerjet cannot guarantee that your personal information will not be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy.

#### Changes To This Privacy Policy

We may amend this policy at any time by sending the amended policy to the email address you provided to us or by posting the amended policy on our site.

#### Questions?

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact us.
